http://www.unitedwayspokane.org/privacypolicy

Skip to main content
HOMEABOUT USMeet Our TeamBoard of DirectorsFinancial AccountabilityCommunity InvestmentsMEDIAVideosNewsPrivacy PolicyFrequently Asked QuestionsCOVID-19COVID 19 ResourcesAll In WashingtonCOVID-19 Response and Recovery FundWashington Mask ChallengeHand Drawings for HeroesHand Drawings for Heroes GalleryOUR WORKOur Partners 2019-2021HealthDomestic ViolenceEducationVelloFinancial StabilityALICE in SpokaneFree Tax PreparationHomelessnessYouth HomelessnessAmeriCorps VISTAEquity Work / Excelerate SuccessCommitment to EquityEmergency Food and Shelter ProgramVisual StoriesCAMPAIGNInvesting in Our CommunityCorporate Engagement ToolsCampaign Coordinator ToolsWorkplace GivingDonor Tax AdvantagesCorporate EngagementMember GroupsBe a VolunteerEmerging Leaders SocietyLeadership CircleTocqueville SocietyEventsKickoff 2020Spokane Philanthropy Awards 2020Fall 2020 OpportunitiesEmerging Leaders Society EventsOVATION 2020 CelebrationInvestment Team 2021CONTACT USCAREERS
Donor Privacy Policy
You are hereHomeABOUT US
WE THANK YOU FOR YOUR TRUST AND PROMISE TO PROTECT BOTH YOUR CHARITABLE INVESTMENT AND YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Our Commitment to Our Donors’ Privacy
As a donor to Spokane County United Way, you have entrusted to us not only your charitable gifts, but personal information as well.  We thank you for your trust and promise to protect both your charitable investment and your personal information in keeping with the highest ethical standards and industry best practices.
We will not sell, share or trade our donors’ names or personal information with any other entity, nor send mailings to our donors on behalf of other organizations.  This policy applies to all information received by Spokane County United Way, both online and offline, which may include but is not limited to: website, social media, electronic donations, event registrations, written pledge cards, and oral communications.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
Spokane County United Way collects personal data only for its intended business purpose.  Information including but not limited to name, address, phone number, email, and charitable gift amount, collected from donors will not be sold for any purpose.
Unless you as a donor requests to be anonymous on the donor pledge form your information, limited to some or all of the following: name, address, email address, and gift amount, may be disclosed in recognition materials and / or distributed to the ultimate recipient of any funds contributed by you through the donor designation option made available as a service of Spokane County United Way.  This is to allow the recipient agency to thank you for your gift.
Our contracts with third-party vendors that help us with printing and other services have strict confidentiality and security provisions that hold them to Spokane County United Way’s privacy standards.  Spokane County United Way allows access to your information to auditors and other third parties only as mandated by regulatory requirements.
Data Security and Protection
Within Spokane County United Way we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in keeping with industry standards and best practices, and we review and adjust these safeguards regularly in response to advances in technology.  We limit access to confidential information to those employees who need it to perform their duties, and hold those employees to a strict code of ethics and confidentiality.  Spokane County United Way’s Privacy Policy extends online.  Online donations and event registration information are transmitted via a secure server.  Both Spokane County United Way and our technology partners for online credit card processing meet Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance standards.
Contact Us
Please contact us if you have a comment, question or wish to update your information.
Lisa Curtis, Director of Communications and Marketing / Spokane County United Way920 N. Washington, Suite 100, Spokane, WA  99201Office:  509-838-6581 Direct Line:  509-324-5029 Email:  lisac@unitedwayspokane.org
EDUCATIONHEALTHFINANCIAL STABILITY
Impact Calculator
Enter an amount to see the impact of your donation:
